hollywoodhotmoms.com 2017-11-17

# Privacy Policy | Hot Moms Club

[vc_row][vc_column][vc_column_text] 

Hot Moms Club Tm. takes very seriously the private nature of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you register for and view our Buzz Email or visit our Web Site. Please read this notice carefully.

Personal Information

To receive your HMC and Insider Rewards e-mails, and rewards we require your e-mail address. Similarly, to provide you with text messaging services, we need your phone number and your provider information. So that we may provide you with additional services, we may also request your name, geographical coordinates, and telephone number. HMC  does not collect any other personally identifiable information that you do not expressly provide. HMC a will never sell, rent or share your personal information, including your e-mail address, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission, if you accept a reward, that 3rd party will get your information so they can send you a reward. HMC  may share your personal information for the purpose of delivering our e-mail to you or as required by law.

Non-Personal Information

We may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as annual income, buying preferences or age, also known as demographic and profile data, though this information is optional. We may use this data to improve our Buzz email and site and/or tailor your experience, showing you or delivering you by email content that we think might be of interest to you, and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising in HMC and Insider Rewards emails or on our site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

Usage Information

In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, HMC may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers’ use of our emails and site. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our emails, site and services. For example, this information will tell us how often a user opens the HMC email, how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites subscribers came, and to what other sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently deliver your emails.

Review and Access

Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

How to Unsubscribe

You can unsubscribe from receiving HMC and Insider Rewards emails at any time. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the footer of any HMC,  HMC Buzz or Insider Rewards email or on the bottom of the HMC  homepage and following the instructions. We, of course, do not want to see you go, but if for any reason you want to leave us and have trouble doing so please email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2d4c494044436d5a5a5a034542594042405e4e41584f034e4240)

Choice/Opt-Out

If we ever send you information by email concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no future notices.

Third Party Advertising

Some of the ads appearing on our HMC Email and Web Site may be delivered to you by our Web advertising partner or partners. Information about your visit to a partner site or sites, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about our advertising partner or partners, cookies, and how to “opt-out”, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) for more information.

Occasionally, you’ll get an email marked “dedicated” or “sponsored” in the subject line and in the email header. These emails are not necessarily reflective of the opinions of the editorial staff. They are content paid for by our sponsors. You can unsubscribe from receiving these emails, however, if you do so, you will no longer receive HMC unsponsored emails either. Please see “How to unsubscribe.”

Tracking

Like most sites, HMC .com makes use of browser “cookies.” Cookies are small text files placed on your computer’s hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly recognize you and simplify your user experience. HMC will never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that is unrelated to our site or services.

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

Links to Other Sites

As part of the service, HMC will create links allowing you to access third party sites. HMC  is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites’ individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

Security

All information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

Modification to this Policy

HMC may change this policy, but we’ll post any changes here, so be sure to check back for future information.

Opting Out of Interest-Based Mobile Ads

If you choose to opt out of interest-based ads on your mobile device, you’ll still see ads but they may not be related to factors such as your interests, previous visits to other websites, or demographic details. To do so, please follow directions for your device below:

iOS – <https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074>  
Android – <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this policy, the Buzz email or our site in general, please email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#aec7c0c8c1eededbdccbd9c1d980cdc1c3)

[/vc_column_text][vc_column_text] 

Hot Moms Club Tm and Hollywood Hot Moms Products, Inc. takes very seriously the private nature of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you register for and view our Buzz Email or visit our Web Site. Please read this notice carefully.

Personal Information

To receive your HMC and HHM e-mails, we require your e-mail address. Similarly, to provide you with text messaging services, we need your phone number and your provider information. So that we may provide you with additional services, we may also request your name, geographical coordinates, and telephone number. HMC and HHM does not collect any other personally identifiable information that you do not expressly provide. HMC and HHM will never sell, rent or share your personal information, including your e-mail address, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission. HMC and HHM may share your personal information for the purpose of delivering our e-mail to you or as required by law.

Non-Personal Information

We may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as annual income, buying preferences or age, also known as demographic and profile data, though this information is optional. We may use this data to improve our Buzz email and site and/or tailor your experience, showing you or delivering you by email content that we think might be of interest to you, and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising in HMC  emails or on our site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

Usage Information

In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, HMC  may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers’ use of our Buzz email and site. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our Buzz email, site and services. For example, this information will tell us how often a user opens the Buzz email, how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites subscribers came, and to what other sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently deliver your emails.

Review and Access

Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

How to Unsubscribe

You can unsubscribe from receiving HMC emails at any time. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the footer of any HMC email or on the bottom of the HMC  homepage and following the instructions. We, of course, do not want to see you go, but if for any reason you want to leave us and have trouble doing so please email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3756535a5e5977404040195f58435a585a44545b42551954585a)

Choice/Opt-Out

If we ever send you information by email concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no future notices.

Third Party Advertising

Some of the ads appearing in our  Emails and Web Site may be delivered to you by our Web advertising partner or partners. Information about your visit to a partner site or sites, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about our advertising partner or partners, cookies, and how to “opt-out”, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) for more information.

You will get an email marked “dedicated” or “sponsored” in the subject line and in the email header. These emails are not necessarily reflective of the opinions of the editorial staff. They are content paid for by our sponsors. You can unsubscribe from receiving these emails, however, if you do so, you will no longer receive HMC unsponsored emails either. Please see “How to unsubscribe.”

Tracking

Like most sites, HMC .com makes use of browser “cookies.” Cookies are small text files placed on your computer’s hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly recognize you and simplify your user experience. HMC will never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that is unrelated to our site or services.

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

Links to Other Sites

As part of the service, HMC  will create links allowing you to access third party sites. HMC  is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites’ individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

Security

All information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

Modification to this Policy

HMC  may change this policy, but we’ll post any changes here, so be sure to check back for future information.

Opting Out of Interest-Based Mobile Ads

If you choose to opt out of interest-based ads on your mobile device, you’ll still see ads but they may not be related to factors such as your interests, previous visits to other websites, or demographic details. To do so, please follow directions for your device below:

iOS – <https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074>  
Android – <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en>

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this policy, the Buzz email or our site in general, please email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#20494e534944455260484f544d4f4d53434c55420e434f4d)

[/vc_column_text][/vc_column][vc_column][/vc_column][/vc_row]
